[ Birds chirping ]
[ People screaming ]
[ Rumbling ]
[ Zapping, beeping ]
[ Vehicle approaching ]
[ Dramatic music playing ]
[ Engine revs ]
[ Tire screeches ]
♪♪
[ Zapping, beeping ]
Yaaaaaah!
[ Growls ]
♪♪
[ Somber music plays ]
[ Zapping, beeping ]
50 years have passed,
but I do not age.
Time has lost its effect on me.
[ Exhales sharply ]
[ Laughs maniacally ]
Yet the suffering
continues.
Aku's grasp chokes the past,
present, and future.
Hope is lost.
Gotta get back,
back to the past.
Samurai Jack.
♪♪
All: Aaaaaaaakuuuuuuuuuu.
[ Screaming ]
[ Gong bangs ]
[ Baby crying ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Babies crying ]
[ Gong bangs ]
[ Crying continues ]
Seven daughters
to do your bidding, Master.
They will succeed where
so many others have failed,
and we will find favor
in your glory.
[ Dramatic music playing ]
[ Shrieks ]
♪♪
[ Tires screeching ]
[ Explosion ]
[ Birds chirping ]
[ Dramatic music playing ]
[ Engine revs ]
[ Chirping ]
[ Birds chirping ]
[ Breathes deeply ]
[ Slurps ]
Father: Why?
Why?
Why have you forsaken us?
Have you forgotten,
my son?
No. No.
Help!
Help me, son!
You must!
Son,
you are forgetting us!
No.
You --
You never came back.
You left us.
You abandoned
your purpose.
I haven't!
You left us all to...
Many voice:
[ Distorted ] Die!
[ All screaming ]
Ahh!
[ Dramatic music playing ]
[ Horse whinnying ]
[ Birds chirping ]
[ Crickets chirping ]
[ Owl hooting ]
Father: Son?
Father?
Why?
I -- I --
We've been waiting for you
so long,
but you never came back.
No, Father, Aku destroyed
the way home.
I don't understand!
You were the only one
who could save us!
Father.
He destroyed everything!
Everything is burning!
You've forgotten
your purpose!
[ Distorted voice ]
You've forsaken us!
[ Screaming ]
[ Horse whinnies ]
Ahh!
[ Tires screech ]
[ Dramatic music playing ]
Ugh!
Any mistake is
certain death,
and death
is our failure.
♪♪
[ Growls ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Birds chirping ]
Bask in the glory of
what our master has created.
Admire its beauty,
but know that the Samurai
is out there
leaving a wake of devastation
wherever he goes.
That's why, my sweet Ashi,
the daughters of Aku
must stay focused,
never relent,
always attack.
Teach this one
a lesson.
[ Dramatic music playing ]
Stop!
The weak
have no place with Aku.
[ Bones crunching ]
Are you weak?
[ Grunting, gasping ]
[ Grunting,
breathing heavily ]
Are you weak?!
Ahh!
Yes.
Aku's fire stirs
inside all of you.
To defeat the one,
your senses must be sharp.
Their time is almost at hand.
Once they succeed,
you will again honor us
with your presence.
[ Vehicle approaching ]
[ Birds chirping ]
[ Engine shuts off ]
[ Dramatic music playing ]
Samurai Jack!
Man, it is good to see you,
babe.
What took you so long?
I decimated this village
days ago
just for you.
Oh, wait.
This is you, right?
I mean,
who could recognize you
with all that gear
and ruggedness, baby?
I'll tell you who --
me.
[ Scatting ]
Scaramouch the Merciless,
the Pied Piper of Ruination,
the Crooner of Carnage,
the Ambassador of Annihilation,
the Eradicator of All, baby.
Also known as Aku's
most favorite assassin, babe.
Oh, there it is, babe,
the world-famous scowl.
Well, come on, Sammy, baby.
Whip it out.
You know what
I'm talking about --
that crazy sword.
Let's get slicin' and dicin',
swingin' and bashin',
hackin' and slashin',
babe.
Wait.
Back off, "Beardsly."
Where is your sword,
huh?
I don't see it.
Oh?
[ Laughs ]
No, no, no, no, no,
babe!
Don't tell me
you lost your sword.
[ Metal clanging ]
[ Laughs ]
Okay, Jacky, baby,
you just make with the scowl
while I make with the phone
and call Aku.
[ Keypad beeping ]
[ Line ringing ]
Aku: Who is this?!
Aku, baby,
how's it hanging, boss?
Guess what I --
What? Hello?!
Ooh,
nice choreography, babe.
You haven't lost a step.
Well, then, let's dance.
[ Jazzy flute music playing ]
[ Dramatic music playing ]
[ Growls ]
You know, babe, I wasn't crazy
about the front scruff,
but I am groovin'
on the mane.
♪♪
Child: Jack.
Help us, Jack.
[ Gasps ]
Help us.
-Help us!
-Help us, Jack!
Please, no.
You must understand.
That samurai has gone
beaucoup cuckoo.
[ Children speaking
indistinctly ]
[ Dramatic music playing ]
[ Horse whinnies ]
[ Horse snorting ]
[ Jazzy flute music playing ]
[ Dramatic music playing ]
[ Flute music stops ]
Hey, you might have destroyed
my magic flute,
but you can't destroy the
musical magic that is me, babe.
[ Scatting ]
[ High-pitched whine ]
Dig that beautiful sound,
baby.
Hey, babe, I told you --
I'm Aku's favorite.
No one plays the blades
like I do.
[ Blades squealing ]
No one!
[ Scatting ]
[ Dagger squealing ]
Well, it's been fun, Jack-o,
but I got to move on.
Au revoir.
That's French for,
"You're dead, babe."
[ Dramatic music playing ]
Well, babe, time for me
to shuffle offstage.
Looks like
you're the headliner now.
[ Grunts ]
[ Scats ]
That's all, babe.
[ Dramatic music playing ]
Ashi.
♪♪
Your training is complete.
Go! Kill!
You are seven,
but now you wear
the face of one,
one purpose for which
you were born --
to kill the Samurai!
♪ Watch out ♪
♪ Back to the past ♪
♪ Jack, Jack, Jack, Jack, Jack ♪
♪ Gotta get back,
back to the past, Samurai Jack ♪
♪ Watch out ♪
♪ Jack, Jack, Jack, Jack, Jack ♪
♪ Gotta get back ♪
♪ Jack, Jack, Jack ♪
♪ Samurai Jack ♪
♪ Jack, Jack, Jack, Jack, Jack ♪