50 years have passed.
But I do not age.
Time has lost its effect on me.
[ Exhales sharply ]
[ Laughs maniacally ]
Yet the suffering continues.
Aku's grasp chokes the past,
present, and future.
Hope is lost.
Got to get back --
back to the past.
Samurai Jack.
♪♪
[ Bird chirping ]
[ Crows caw ]
[ Woodpecker clicking
in distance ]
Aaagh!
[ Grunting, gasping ]
[ Crows caw ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
[ Creak ]
Aah!
[ Dramatic music plays ]
[ Crows caw ]
-Murderer!
-Killer!
Crows: [ Chanting ] Killer!
Murderer! Killer! Murderer!
Murderer! Murderer!
Killer!
-No.
-Killer! Killer!
-Murderer!
No.
Murderer!
No!
They chose the path!
They chose!
[ Crows click ]
[ Chain creaking ]
[ Birds chirp in distance ]
[ Growls ]
Aah!
[ Grunting ]
Die! Die!
Why won't you die?
Scum!
Aku will be triumphant!
I will undo the evil
that is you, samurai!
I will kill you!
As long as I have breath
in my body,
I will strike you down!
Long live
the glory of Aku!
You are very troubled.
And very confused.
Aku is the evil one,
not me.
I've met machines
that are programmed
with such hate and lies,
but never a human.
Deceiver!
Worm! Scum!
Now you're
just repeating yourself.
[ Grunts, growls ]
I wonder if it is possible
for her to ever believe
that Aku is the evil
and not me?
Lecherous snake!
Mm, perhaps not.
[ Rumbling ]
[ Creature roars ]
[ Dramatic music plays ]
[ Grunts ]
Are you kidding me?
[ Gasps ]
Jack: [ Grunts ]
[ Rumbling, growling ]
Whew.
[ Gasps ]
[ Coughs ]
[ Laughs maniacally ]
My Lord and master, Aku,
may it please you
for all eternity --
The samurai is dead.
Um...
I'm right here.
Fool! We've been swallowed
by a monolithic creature.
You're dead.
I've been
inside giant creatures before.
I'll find a way out.
Stop. Enough!
No!
I will never stop!
Yes, yes, I know --
till your dying breath.
But once you see
how misguided you are,
you will see the truth
about Aku.
[ Footsteps approaching ]
[ Dramatic music plays ]
[ Creatures chattering ]
[ Creature roars ]
[ Creature growls ]
[ Creatures roar, growl ]
[ Screams ]
[ Creatures roaring ]
[ Gasps ]
Be still!
Crazy woman!
Can you not see
that I am saving your life?
Aaaaaagh!
Uh, hello?
[ Creatures growling ]
[ Blade clatters ]
[ Dramatic music continues ]
[ Creatures snarl, growl ]
[ Rumbling, growling ]
[ Electricity crackling ]
High Priestess: Ashi?
Ashi?
Kill the samurai!
[ Gasping ]
Jack?
What are we doing, Jack?
Waiting.
Waiting for what?
You know the way out.
Let's just go.
No.
She's another innocent.
"Innocent"?
Are you mad?
She's pure evil.
She's lost her way.
[Chuckles] You'd know
about that, wouldn't you?
I don't want to talk
to you anymore.
[ Blows ]
Well, then, maybe
you'll talk to me.
Leave me alone.
Jack: I don't want
to talk to you, either.
I don't know why
you keep bringing this up.
[ Creature growls lightly ]
Look, why do you
always have to get involved?
She chose her way,
and now she has to live
with the consequences.
You'll never understand
that it's all my fault!
She's here because of me.
She's gone.
What?
[ Low growling ]
Okay, well, that's that.
Lets get out of here.
No.
Ugh, you're going to save
her life again, aren't you?
Yes.
[ Dramatic music plays ]
[ Creature growling,
blows landing ]
Jack: [ Grunts ]
[ Chains jingle ]
You're welcome.
I'd be happier
as that creature's excrement
than be grateful to you.
What did you expect,
a hug and a kiss?
[ Dramatic music plays ]
By Aku's will,
you will die in here.
There is no hope for you,
foolish samurai.
Aku is the master of masters
and will end you!
[ Electricity crackling ]
No matter
what you have planned for me,
I will never buckle,
never waiver.
Your death is certain!
Aku desires it!
[ Echoing ] Aku has made
a world of wonders,
and you have soiled it!
Aku is the father
of all fathers!
His greatness
cannot be measured!
You are a parasite, samurai,
feeding off Aku's generosity!
Aku, my master,
this fool knows not
of your greatness,
your kindness,
your understanding!
Jack: Enough!
Every thing, every word,
every thought
that you know is wrong!
Aku -- Aku is the one
that has laid waste
to the beauty
of this world!
He has destroyed
mother nature!
Where do you think
we are?!
Aku has unleashed
these monstrosities
upon our world,
and they feed off his carnage.
Liar!
Believe what you may.
But if you open your eyes
and let go of the hate,
you will see the truth.
Die.
[ Clinking ]
Rain?
[ Grunts ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Needles clinking ]
Well, um...
I guess we should
get this over with.
You know, uh,
many people pay money for this.
It's called acupuncture.
Never mind.
[ Clinking continues ]
[ Low, rhythmic rumbling ]
[ Liquid pattering ]
[ Electricity crackling ]
[ Wind whistles ]
[ Creature chitters ]
Whew.
[ Dramatic music plays ]
[ Clatter ]
I like the back fur.
You look hideous.
From you, "hideous" is
quite acceptable.
Thank you.
[ Wind gusts, whistles ]
We're close.
[ Gasps ]
Aaaaaaah!
[ Vine creaking ]
[ Dramatic music plays ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Creatures squeaking ]
Even in the bowels
of the darkest of creatures,
there is beautiful light.
[ Wind gusts ]
[ Birds calling ]
[ Hissing ]
[ Uplifting music plays ]
Seems simple enough --
Use the flying creatures
to escape
and not fall
into the pool of acid.
Right.
[ Dramatic music plays ]
[ Creature squawks ]
[ Creature growls ]
[ Electricity crackles ]
Whew.
[ Creature growls ]
[ Creature snarls ]
We're slowing down.
No, please, faster.
Faster!
[ Creature roars ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Insects chirping ]
[ Coughs ]
[ Coughing ]
[ Breathes heavily ]
[ Beetle buzzing ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Dramatic music plays ]
Wait!
High Priestess: Ashi.
These frivolous distractions
are poisons for your mission.
They are not part
of Aku's order.
High Priestess: [ Echoing ]
Not part of Aku's order.
[ Dramatic music plays ]
♪ Watch out ♪
♪ Jack, Jack, Jack ♪
♪ Jack, Jack, Jack, Jack ♪
♪ Got to get back,
back to the past ♪
♪ Samurai Jack ♪
♪ Watch out ♪
♪ Jack, Jack,
Jack, Jack, Jack ♪
♪ Watch out ♪
♪ Got to get back ♪
♪ Samurai Jack ♪
♪ Wa-Watch out ♪